## **Ben Myers**

UCLA undergraduate pursuing B.S. in Mathematics with three years of customer service experience, one year of educational experience, and five years of computer programming experience. Involved in software development, management, and business growth.

Personal involvements include UCLA Chorale, UCLA Sigma Eta Pi, Bruin Entrepreneurs, and the UCLA Founder's Club.

benl.myers01@gmail.com +1 561-374-4627 benlmyers.com github.com/benlmyers

**Technical Skills** 

Languages

Swift JavaScript C++ Python Java HTML + CSS C# Rust

**Environments and Tools** 

SwiftUI, UIKit React, RN, Vue JavaX, Swing Unity, Unreal Blender FL Studio + Logic Adobe PS, AI, PR Git + Github

**Education** 

Alexander W. Dreyfoos School of the Arts
H.S. Diploma, 2020 | 4.0 GPA | 5.037 HPA | 1510 SAT | 33 ACT

B.S. Mathematics, 2024 | 3.483 Major GPA

B.S. Mathematics, 2024 | 3.483 Major GPA

**Experience** 

Founder and CEO Jan 2021 - Present

Flowductive - Self-employed

Brought Flowductive to Startup UCLA Summer Accelerator as the youngest solo founder.

- Self-built 5 iterations of a iOS + macOS productivity app; web landing page; and 3 open-source Swift packages.
- · Raised and managed company's socials, internship cohort of 18; and captured interest from industry-leading VCs.
- · Spoke at several UCLA startup programs, including events hosted by Bruin Labs and Bruin Entrepreneurs.

Co-Founder and CTO Jun 2022 - Present

Poppin Technologies - Part-time

www.ioinpoppin.com

www.flowductive.com

- Rebuilt mobile app, data structure, and UI/UX from ground-up with a modern Swift tech stack.
- · Improved end-user experience with dynamic content, deep linking, and Stripe payment integration.
- · Led web platform development with Firebase integration, online payments, and ticketing.

iOS Developer Nov 2020 - Present

Yatco - Full-time

www.yatco.com

- Improved web SEO for a yachting MLS website with 600+ visitors/day in traffic.
- Parsed 2000+ yacht builder data objects from sites into JSON using a custom Python script.
- Developed leading-edge mobile Charter/Consumer application, disrupting a \$10 billion market.

iOS Developer Dec 2021 - Feb 2022

Edvora - Internship

www.edvora.com

- · Stabilized and widened the mobile device compatibility of a global SaaS education solution.
- Improved the quality and scalability of the future of Ed-tech in education, technology, finance, and enterprise.

Code Sensei Jan 2020 - Apr 2021

Code Ninias - Part-time

www.codeninias.com

- Taught kids ages 7-14 how to code in languages such as Swift, JavaScript, Lua, and Python.
- · Directed, supervised, and taught children coding skills during several themed summer camps.
- · Hosted and assisted with routine online code learning sessions over Zoom.

## **Customer Service Agent**

Dec 2016 - Jun 2020

Publix - Part-time

www.publix.com

- · Worked as an item bagger, then a cashier, then a customer service agent, for one year each.
- Recognized 7 times for outstanding customer service and continually achieved "Exceeding Expectations" and "Role Model" marks in biannual performance evaluations.
- Promoted twice for demonstrated leadership and proactiveness.